so we talk about IC Lumbard we are the
leading we the number one private
General Insurance company in the country
so last year we did almost 25,000 of
Premium 2,000 of profit almost of profit
after tax we issued around 3.62 CR
policies we serviced uh 29 lakhs St that
was settled so we have presence in
almost thousand locations we are serving
to offices and our uh
key basically app the multi Channel
distribution that we have in I lomard so
we have a strong force of almost 1.2
lakh advisers we have 105 digital
Partnerships almost all oems have been
covered we have we are partnering with
them uh 300 plus financial institutions
so basically Banks uh nbfcs you name it
and we have a TI up there 230 plus
Affinity Partners we have and 600 plus
districts wherein a is present in some
of the pl
form the most important uh now we let us
talk about the health insurance overview
of and we are also the diabetes capital
of the world so if you see 177% people
are having diabetes in the country so
then retail Health penetration is all so
one product cannot fit all the customers
in the country so you'll have to have
different multiple products Bing to CER
to all the
customers uh customers are having
inadequate coverages they are they want
fair pricing they want transparency in
claims so this is what a customer needs
when he looks for a health insurance
govern
[Music]
so Elevate wherein we say the power of
infinite personalization powered by AI
so if you see the sign of in finance to
a
customer so let me start uh with this
first unique cover that we had launched
so it is called infinite care let me
give you an example to make you
understand about this cover so if a
customer buys a policy wherein he Ops
for a sum insure of 5 lakh rupees and he
says I will off for this infinite care
cover as well once in a lifetime he can
take an unlimited
claim so for just for an example he took
he took a 5 lak policy and uh he had a
kidney problem right so that 5 lakh got
exhausted now the next year he again
wants a kidney transplant now that the
doctor gave him a bill of 50 lakh rupees
he has a policy of only 5 lakh rupees
how come 50 lakhs will be serviced but
if the customer has taken this cover so
he can get once in a lifetime any claim
amount so 50 LH also if he gets a claim
it will be paid
so this is a industry first cover that
we are talking about uh this is being
launched second is power booster uh
where in we
say years it becomes one so it is again
in finite till the time customer is
there he's paying the premium he's ring
the policy it gets added
up the industry leading feature once
again we now are not limiting any
customer on some so some customer will
need one some some customer will need
features that we have in our Elevate
product so Elevate is a product that is
buil on a modular CH and customer
whatever he needs he can actually pick
and choose those covers so we have
approximately 18 add-on coverages in
this program in this product so we in as
for the need of the customer he can pick
and choose the add on what is relevant
for him he can pick and choose and take
the policy so these are the major uh
feur features that we have first is
infinite here then power inite Su and
jump so uh myself so tan I'm vice
president for health agency so we take
care of Health product so recently we
talked about the Elevate product uh that
we have launched so there are the four
major features about the product that I
again with you so infinite care was one
where the customer can take an amount of
Unum of amount of claim in his once once
in his lifetime then was a power booster
can where in his policy actually uh gets
doubled every year so if he buy a 10
lakh cap policy it becomes 20 lakhs the
next year this is again an add on cover
next 10 years a 10 lak policy will
become a 1 CR policy and so on and so
forth right third was the jump start
that we talked about where in a customer
if he has a ped so he can get the cover
from 31st day as in the normal policy if
you see it PD has different different uh
somebody covers it in 2 years some
covers it in 3 years with jump start it
it gets covered in 31st day only then
there was a unlimited some insured
add-on feature that we had where a
customer can buy unlimited some insured
policy so these are the major features
that we have in our product apart from
these features we have some 18 add-on
covers that a customer can buy depending
upon his needs so we had b in a modular
CHC product right wherein if a customer
needs some of the other on he can pick
and choose and he can get a premium and
get his policy done so now it's totally
dependent on the customer see again this
product is again based on AI that we
talked about so we'll actually give
customer an added Advantage we'll
recommend him a plan this is the best
suited plan for that particular customer
so if depending upon the demography
depending upon his family size depending
upon what age he is into right depending
upon his income everything so we'll
curate a plan for him and we will
recommend a plan to that customer so
these are the major features that we
have launched in this product what do
the main